<doc>
  <page p="1" label="1">1
New Team Member Guide
Employee Service Center
Cox Automove Global Learning
Cox Automove Global Learning
1</page>
  <page p="2" label="2">2
About This Guide
Starting a new job is exciting and challenging. We also understand that it can be a
stressful time.
We have developed this onboarding guide to help reduce some of the uncertainty and
help you become a successful member of Cox Automotive. This guide provides you with
practical information and resources to help you integrate into your new role.
Adjusting to a new job and environment takes time. To help you with your transition, we
have divided this process into sections:
1. Welcome to Cox
2. Soft Skills
3. Tools and Resources
Throughout this manual you will see these call out icons, which will direct you to other
resources or to learn more:
Good to know!
Exercises
Real World Examples
Cox Automove Global Learning
2</page>
  <page p="3" label="3">3
Important Information
Attendance
Your regularly scheduled shift is assigned by your supervisor/manager and adherence to the
attendance policy is required. You are expected to be on time to your workstation each work
period.
Occasionally, situations arise which may prevent you from reporting to work on time. While your job is
important, supervisors must make arrangements to cover your work during your absence. If you know you
are going to be late, you must contact a supervisor or manager as quickly as possible. All absences,
including tardiness must be reported personally by you to your direct supervisor or manager, unless
medically unable to do so.
Acceptable methods of contact are: text message, voicemail or email to your direct supervisor or manager.
Contact Information
Name
Kimberly Fraites
Kimberly.Fraites@coxautoinc.com
Open
Rochelle McCullough
Shelli.McCullough@coxautoinc.com
Jason Boddie
Jason.Boddie@coxautoinc.com
Debbie Urzua
Deborah.Urzua@coxautoinc.com
Susan Green
Susan.Green@coxautoinc.com
Simara Williams
Simara.Williams@coxautoinc.com
Cox Automove Global Learning
Position
Sr. Manager
Winter Garden, FL
Sr. Manager
Riverside, CA
Support Supervisor
Winter Garden, FL
Payroll Supervisor
Winter Garden, FL
Leave and Support Supervisor
Riverside, CA
Payroll Supervisor
Riverside, CA
Trainer
Orlando, FL
Contact Information
Office: 407-905-3272
Cell: 407-865-4892
Office:
Cell:
Office: 407-905-3275
Cell: 407-848-7996
Office: 407-905-3273
Cell: 407-961-9095
Office: 951-351-4630
Cell: 951-743-9873
Office: 951-351-4607
Cell: 951-901-5866
Office: 407-905-3276
Cell: 407-961-8605
3</page>
  <page p="4" label="4">4
Attendance Forms
Cox Automotive’s Paid Time Off (PTO) plan provides eligible team members with the
flexibility to use paid time off to meet their personal needs.
Cox Automotive hourly team members are required to
complete and submit a written or electronic request to
their manager for all requested time off. Time off may
not be taken until the PTO request is approved by a
manager.
PTO requests should be submitted to a manager for
approval as soon as possible, but no less than the
week prior to the requested time off.
All hourly, non-exempt team members must be
compensated for all the time worked. All hourly,
non-exempt team members must clock in and out on a
daily basis, including in and out for a meal break.
If you clock out but continue to
perform work or, if you log in from
home to check or reply to emails you
must submit a Time Correction form
to your manager.
If you fail to clock in or out from your
shift or meal break, you can use the
Time Correction form to request a
missed punch correction.
Time Correction requests must be
submitted on a daily basis as they
occur.
Cox Automove Global Learning
4</page>
  <page p="5" label="5">5
Module 1:
In this section, you will learn more about:
Our Company
Who is Cox Automotive
Our Values
Org Chart
Our Brands
The Employee Service Center
Cox Automove Global Learning
5</page>
  <page p="6" label="6">6
Our Company
Cox Enterprises is a leading communications, media and automotive services company. With revenues of
$18 billion and approximately 55,000 employees, the company's major operating subsidiaries include:
 Cox Communications (cable television distribution, high-speed Internet access, telephone,
home security and automation, commercial telecommunications and advertising solutions)
 Cox Media Group (television and radio stations, digital media, newspapers and advertising
sales rep firms)
 Cox Automotive (automotive-related auctions, financial services, media and software
solutions)
The company's major national brands include AutoTrader, Kelley Blue Book, Manheim, Savings.com and
Valpak.
Cox Automove Global Learning
6</page>
  <page p="7" label="7">7
Who is Cox Automotive
Our Vision:
Transform the way the world buys, sells and
owns vehicles.
Co
x Automoti
v
e is the world’s leader in vehicle remarketing services and digital marketing and
software solutions for automotive dealers and consumers.
Our goal is to simplify the trusted exchange of vehicles and maximize value for dealers, manufacturers
and car shoppers. We’ve built the industry’s strongest family of more than 25 brands to provide industry-leading
digital marketing, software, financial, wholesale and e-commerce solutions to help our clients
thrive in a rapidly changing automotive marketplace.
Our Mission:
To provide key solutions that create greater
efficiencies in the automotive ecosystem.
We build solutions. We drive innovation.
We embrace new technology.
Cox Automove Global Learning
7</page>
  <page p="8" label="8">8
Our Values
 Our TEAM MEMBERS are our most important resource.
 We value DIVERSITY and INCLUSION.
 Our CLIENTS are our lifeblood.
 We are INNOVATIVE.
 We make a positive difference in our COMMUNITIES.
Cox Automove Global Learning
8</page>
  <page p="9" label="9">9
Org Chart
Cox Automove Global Learning
9</page>
  <page p="10" label="10">10
Our Brands
Cox Automotive businesses operate in five core focus areas with a domestic and global presence.
Our brands lead the industry with best-in-class offerings that connect all the pieces of the automotive
puzzle that our customers live with every day into one scalable solution. We bring together the best and
brightest partners and teams to create value, efficiency and opportunity for our customers to run their
businesses more effectively and profitably.
Exercises
1. Select a brand from the list above. Use the internet and other resources, to learn more
about the selected brand. Share your thoughts with the team.
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________________
Cox Automove Global Learning
_
_</page>
  <page p="11" label="11">11
The Employee Service Center
The Employee Service Center (ESC) currently supports the entire Cox Automotive population across all
business units in the entire US; including Puerto Rico and Hawaii.
Two Locations - One Team!
Riverside, CA
Opened in 2011 after an expansion to support
all Manheim auction locations
Winter Garden, FL
Opened in 2009 to support the Florida
Manheim auction locations
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
  <page p="12" label="12">12
Our Org Structure
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
  <page p="13" label="13">13
Areas We Support
The Employee Service Center (ESC) focuses on the centralization of key operations; such as:
 Payroll
 Benefits
 Leave Management
This centralization allows for the standardization of pay and work rules,
consistency in transactional process and a better customer experience.
Systems and Tools
In addition to processing payroll, managing benefits
and leave of absences, our support extends through many different systems and tools:
 Compass
 SAS (Salary Administration Solution)
 Spark
 Manager Center/Manager Self-Service
 Kronos
 PeopleSoft Time &amp; Labor
 Learning Lane
 Fuel
 InSite
Exercises
1. Using the materials provided, draw a visual representation of our company and the ESC.
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________________
2. Share your drawing and your thoughts with the team.
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________________
Cox Automove Global Learning
_
_
_
_</page>
  <page p="14" label="14">14
ESC Roles
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
  <page p="15" label="15">15
ESC Community
The ESC Community in Fuel is YOUR space!
The ESC Community is your main source of resources. It is a compilation of great ideas that come directly
from your team. In the Community, you can find quick links to the most commonly used programs and
sites, training documents and best practices.
Exercises
1. Find the ESC Community in Fuel. Describe the steps you took below.
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________________
2. Read an article of your choice from the High Importance section and summarize it.
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________________
3. What information can you find in the HR Tool Belt section?
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________________
4. What information can you find in the Training section?
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________________
Cox Automove Global Learning
_
_
_
_
_
_
_
_</page>
  <page p="16" label="16">16
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
  <page p="17" label="17">17
Module 2:
In this section, you will learn more about:
Email Etiquette
Social Media Use
HIPAA Compliance
Protecting Privacy
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
  <page p="18" label="18">18
Email Etiquette
Email etiquette refers to the principles of behavior one should follow when writing or answering email
messages.
Without basic etiquette, your email can be easily misinterpreted by your reader. Therefore, it is crucial
that you follow the basic rules of etiquette to construct an appropriate tone.
Do
 Use a meaningful subject.
 Use a proper salutation.
 Check for punctuation, spelling and grammar.
 Write in a positive tone.
 Be polite - use please and thank you.
 Use a font that has a professional or neutral
look.
 Try to keep the email brief.
 Re-read before sending.
 Include a proper closing and signature.
 Use your templates when applicable.
Don’t
 Don’t type all in CAPS.
 Avoid slang or text-message type (ex: How r
u?).
 Avoid using negative words.
 Don’t reply all on your email if the message
isn’t relevant to everyone.
 Don’t respond if you’re upset. Take time to
cool off and consider the appropriate response.

 Don’t use sarcasm or rude jokes.
Think twice about whether or not the content of your email is appropriate for virtual correspondence.
Once you hit SEND, anyone might be able to read your email.
Standard Signatures
Team Signature
Personal Signatures
Remember: not all messages are best delivered via email. There are many instances when one should
stop and say: “It’s time to meet or talk in person because we’ve gotten as far as we can through email”.
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
  <page p="19" label="19">19
Email Etiquette Quiz
1. When writing an email message, paragraphs should:
A. Be long
B. Be short
C. Be indented
2. The best way to make several points in one email is to:
A. Include all the points in one paragraph
B. Use lists with bullets or numbers
C. Emphasize by typing in CAPS or use red, bold font
3. The tone of a professional work email should be:
A. Conversational
B. Formal
C. Casual - like the tone you use with your friends
4. When sending an email, you should copy (CC):
A. Everyone in the department
B. Your supervisor and boss, so they know you’re working hard
C. Only those people who absolutely must know
5. When replying to an email, you should:
A. Always reply to all, so that everyone know you replied
B. Reply only to those who need to remain in the conversation or be aware
6. What is the most important thing you should do with every email?
A. Spell check, use full sentence structure and use proper grammar
B. Have a nice greeting: Hi, Hello, etc.
C. Have a proper sign off: Thank you, Sincerely, etc.
D. All of the above
SCORE:
5 - 6 = Great job. Keep emailing!
4 - 3 = You’re ok. Be a little more cautious though. You could learn a few tips.
2 - 1 = You could use some help. Let’s review the email etiquette section again.
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
  <page p="20" label="20">20
Social Media Use
Team members who engage in social media should be aware that their activity can impact Cox
Automotive’s business, the public’s perception of our company and the individual’s personal and
professional reputation.
Real World Examples
1. “Linda” posts a racist rant on social media. Her followers notice where Linda works
through her profile and complaints are filed with her employer thus leading to her
termination.
2. After a rough day at the HR Call Center, “Mary” posts derogatory comments on social
media about a customer and how her boss handled the situation. “Mary’s” co-workers report
the post to her manager. She is terminated for violating the company’s social media policy.
Exercises
1. Find the Employee Handbook in Fuel and read the company’s Social Media policy.
2. Summarize the policy below.
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________________
3. How can this policy help create and maintain your personal brand?
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________________
Cox Automove Global Learning
_
_
_
_</page>
  <page p="21" label="21">21
HIPAA Compliance
The Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act is a federal law designed to protect a subset of
sensitive information, known as protected health information (PHI).
Covered Entity
A covered entity is any person or organization that
provides services, bills or is paid for health care services
in the normal course of business.
Protected Health Information (PHI)
PHI is any information provided to a covered entity that can
be used to identify a patient - whether living or deceased -
that relates to the patient’s past, present or future physical or
mental health or condition. This includes healthcare services
provided and payment for those services.
Any of the following are considered identifiers under HIPAA:
 Patient names
 Telephone numbers
 Fax numbers
 Social Security Numbers
 Drivers license numbers
 Email addresses
 Dates (except year)
 Healthcare record numbers
 Account numbers
 Biometric identifiers
 Health plan beneficiary numbers
 Type of treatment or injury
 Demographic information
 Names of relatives
As a Cox HR representative, you are in a position to receive PHI from healthcare plans and/or team
members. Safeguarding this information is a top priority!
Who does HIPAA apply to?
HIPAA covers all team members covered by a medical and dental plan or a flexible spending account.
This also applies to retirees and team members our on long term disability (LTD) who are covered by Cox
medical plans. While short term disability (STD) and Workers Comp are not governed by HIPAA, you
should never share PHI with Workers Comp vendors or the STD plan.
Real World Examples
1. “Suzie” calls the ESC and during the conversation, she tells the Specialist that her son is a
diabetic and shares the name of their prescription.
2. “Jane” and “Tim” are talking in the lunchroom about their co-worker “Paul”, who was involved
in a car accident the previous night and is in the hospital with multiple fractures.
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
  <page p="22" label="22">22
Protecting Privacy
Personal information can be subcategorized into two types:
Examples of Private and Proprietary Information:
 Planned acquisitions
 Customer lists
 Personal data
 Financial data
 Company policies
 Business processes
 Marketing strategies
 Market expansion plans
 Planned advertising programs
 Prototypes
 Suppliers lists and pricing
 Testing data
 Schematics and software
 Plans for improvement of software or services
Examples of Personally Identifiable Information:
 Financial account information
 Personal identification numbers (PIN)
 Drivers license numbers
 DMV information and driving record history
 Passport number
 Medical information (past, present or future)
 Digitalized or electronic signatures
 Insurance related information
 Collections history
 Biometrics data
Cox Automove Global Learning
 Personal email address
 Personal postal address
 User names
 Employee ID number
 Bill / invoice images
 Social Security Number (any portion)
 Date of birth
 Place of birth
 Mother’s maiden name
 Unlisted telephone numbers</page>
  <page p="23" label="23">23
How can I protect our customers’ private information?
Privacy Do’s and Don’ts
 Use approved methods to securely transmit or
distribute personal information
 Use approved methods to store personal
information
Exercises
1. Find the SafeSend application on the ESC Community in Fuel.
____________________________________________________________________
2. Log in to SafeSend and view the web tutorial.
____________________________________________________________________
3. Upload and send a file to the person sitting next to you.
____________________________________________________________________
4. Discuss what other steps you can take to keep information private and secured.
____________________________________________________________________
Cox Automove Global Learning
_
_
_
_
 Do not share PeopleSoft screenshots or other
information with outside parties; including
current or former team members.
 Do not store personal information on
unauthorized devices or communication
services.</page>
  <page p="24" label="24">24
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
  <page p="25" label="25">25
Module 3:
In this section, you will learn more about:
Online Resources
Collaboration Tools
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
  <page p="26" label="26">26
Online Resources
Fuel is Cox Automotive’s company-wide intranet portal. From breaking
news to on-the-job resources, Fuel is home to all things Cox Automotive!!
With Fuel, you can share your thoughts and ideas, follow what your colleagues and team are doing and
get updates from other parts of the company!
My Profile
Top
Stories
Click on the
spyglass to
search for
topics of
interest
Exercises
1. View and update your Fuel profile.
____________________________________________________________________
2. Follow one of your colleagues.
____________________________________________________________________
3. What are three top stories in Fuel? Like one of those articles.
____________________________________________________________________
4. Run a search for Fuel Navigation Overview. Watch the Navigation overview video. Share
your thoughts below.
____________________________________________________________________
5. What are some of the Tools available on Fuel?
____________________________________________________________________
Cox Automove Global Learning
_
_
_
_
_</page>
  <page p="27" label="27">27
InSite is your primary channel for company
information and business related tasks.
Via InSite team members can view and print pay stubs, enroll in benefits, view employee discounts,
update their personal information, update W-4 information, set up direct deposit and much, much more!
1
2
4
3
The Home Page provides access to a wealth of information:
1. Navigation Bar – Your navigation bar provides access to all the pages within InSite. My Tools
provides access to all the self-service tools
2. Employee Directory and Press Releases – In this section, you can use the employee directory to
find the contact information for any employee across all Cox companies or read our company’s
latest press releases.
3. Quick Links – The Quick Links section provides you with easy access to some of the most common
areas within InSite
4. Latest News – In this section, you can read the latest company news. Check this section often as
articles change frequently.
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
  <page p="28" label="28">28
HR Direct gives you fast and easy access to information and tools that can help you support team
members as well as learn about Cox’s Payroll and Benefits. Find job aids, forms, training videos, simulations
and much more!
The navigation pane will help you
find information on Benefits, Payroll,
training information and more.
Two areas you might find of
particular use are the Benefits
Resources and Reference Guides.
Cox Automove Global Learning
28</page>
  <page p="29" label="29">29
Exercises
1. Find and view the HR Direct Orientation in the Training Center.
____________________________________________________________________
2. Open the Benefits At A Glance document from the Benefits Toolbox.
____________________________________________________________________
3. What is the definition of live events according to the Life Events Reference Guide?
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________________
4. What areas of HR Direct do you think will be most helpful to you and why?
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________________
5. What is Compass and what information can you find there?
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________________
6. Where would you find information about preparing an online check?
____________________________________________________________________
7. What are some of the resources available to Benefits Specialists?
____________________________________________________________________
8. What are some of the resources available to Payroll Specialists?
____________________________________________________________________
9. What job aids can you find regarding Payroll Year End processing?
____________________________________________________________________
Cox Automove Global Learning
_
_
_
_
_
_
_
_
_
_
_
_</page>
  <page p="30" label="30">30
Learning Navigator is your one-stop spot on Fuel for
finding the right training and development resources
that meet your needs and suit your style of learning.
Here you will find a wide variety of content, ranging
from Learning Lane courses and classroom offerings
to an ever-changing array of videos, podcasts,
articles and more.
How it works...
The Learning Navigator home page provides general Global Learning information and recommendations.
Users can explore content based on competency and filter by the category that best fits their needs to
easily find learning resources suited for their role.
 Formal classes through Learning Lane
 Informal learning opportunities, such as articles, podcasts and videos
How do I get there?
1 1. From the Fuel homepage, click on the u.Center
drop-down.
Click Learning.
2. Welcome to Learning Navigator.
2
Exercise:
1. From Learning Navigator, click on the MENU button to find the Daily Drivers. Read the prior day’s Daily
Driver post. What is the title of the Daily Driver your read? Share your thoughts on that Driver below.
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________________
Cox Automove Global Learning
_
_
_</page>
  <page p="31" label="31">31
Gain practical, valuable
knowledge...
Learning Lane; one of the resources available through Learning Navigator is your primary source of
formal classroom and eLearning content for all Cox Automotive team members.
To access Learning Lane,
click on the MENU icon on
Learning Navigator.
Click on the appropriate
business.
Use the buttons on your
Learning Lane
homepage to explore
learning opportunities
specific to our different
brands and business
units.
You can also access
enterprise-wide
Exercise:
training and resources,
such as personal and
business skills,
courses to help you
grow your career and
more!
1. Log in to Learning Lane and enter the Road Trip section. Click on the eLearning button and watch the Cox
Automotive presentation. In the spaces below, share your thoughts on this presentation.
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________________
Cox Automove Global Learning
_
_</page>
  <page p="32" label="32">32
Bomgar is a remote support solution that allows our specialists to remotely connect to the end-user’s
system.
When should I use Bomgar?
There are three questions you should think about when
working with customers:
1. Is the customer I’m working with good with computers?
2. Can they follow the instructions I’m giving them over the
phone?
3. Have basic troubleshooting steps been able to resolve
the issue?
When the answer to any of these questions is “NO”, you should use Bomgar to assist in resolving the
customer’s issue.
To remote into your customer’s
computer, log in to the
Representative Console and Start
Session.
There are three methods for
connecting with a customer:
 Send an Email
 Choose Consultant
 Generate Session Key
Choose one of these options to begin the support section with the customer.
The customer will be prompted to download Bomgar. When the download is complete and Bomgar is
installed, instruct the customer to accept the Full Terms &amp; Conditions.
From your queue screen, highlight the session
and click Accept.
Click the Start Screen Sharing button to begin the
session.
Instruct the customer to click Allow
You now have shared access/control of your
customer’s computer!
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
  <page p="33" label="33">33
Handling Objections
 Assure your customer that they are working with a professional and they are able to see everything
you are doing. Let them know you understand their concerns.
 Assure your customer that you will not be accessing anything that you do not need in order to
resolve their issue. Make them feel comfortable with your abilities to help them resolve their issue.
 Inform the customer that all Bomgar software is downloaded for this session only and gets
automatically removed as soon as the session ends.
Objecon
I do not trust you connecng to
my computer; could you give my
computer a virus?
Will you have access to my files?
What about the security risk?
Will you be able to access my files
aer the call is over?
Exercises
1. Partner with the person sitting next to you. Using the processes listed above, remote into
their computer. When you have completed the process, allow your partner to remote into your
computer. Discuss any challenges you might have faced working through the steps.
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________
2. Working with your partner, discuss how would you handle a customer that needs Bomgar
assistance but does not want you to remote into their computer. How would you engage the
customer?
____________________________________________________________________
____________________________________________________________________
Cox Automove Global Learning
__
__
Prospecng Preparaon
Once I am connected to your computer, the opon you will select is
for me to “View Only.” I will guide you through the process and will
not take over control of your computer.
I will not have access to any files on your computer, only the current
acve screen.
The connecon we make will be secure and you will not have to
modify any security sengs in order for Bomgar to connect.
No, once the session is closed the current viewing access will end.
__
_</page>
  <page p="34" label="34">34
Box provides cloud based document management and sharing so that you can keep
your files in one place that you can access anywhere
To access, go to Fuel and click on Tools. From the
drop-down menu, click Box.
Through single sign-on, you will be automatically
logged in to your Box account.
Add files or folders for others to see and share.
Click the Upload button to load
files or folders.
Download and install the latest version of
Box Sync for Windows to sync content
between your desktop and your Box
account.
Drag folders from your computer into your
Box folder to sync them with your account
online.
From your Box account,
right click on any folder to
sync it with your desktop.
The blue icon means
the folder is synced.
Exercises
1. Log in to your Box account and download Box Sync.
_______________________________________________________________________________
2. Create a new folder. Upload a new document via your Box Account. Drag and drop a new
document via the Box folder in your Desktop.
_______________________________________________________________________________
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
  <page p="35" label="35">35
Join Me is an online tool that offers screen sharing and online meetings.
Click Join Me from the Tools drop-down menu
on Fuel. You will be directed to the Join Me
webpage.
Type in your email address - Join Me will
recognize your enterprise account. You will not
need to enter your password. Click the Log In
button.
You can personalize your meeting background.
Your background is the photo that attendees see
when they are waiting for your meeting to start.
Exercises
1. Once logged in, personalize the meeting link that you provide to attendees. Provide the link
in the spaces below.
____________________________________________________________________
__
2. Download the Join.Me application to begin hosting meetings. Click on the application to
log in. Start a meeting and share your screen.
____________________________________________________________________
Cox Automove Global Learning
__</page>
  <page p="36" label="36">36
Skype is super efficient way to quickly connect with co-workers! With Skype, you can instant
message, call, video chat, and share documents with peers.
Status:
Available
Busy
Do Not Disturb
Away / Inactive
Offline
Skype Basics
To start a conversation:
To send an instant message:
To end a conversation:
To make a call:
To share a file:
To share your desktop:
Cox Automove Global Learning
Double-click the name of the contact or point at the contact’s picture
and click the IM button.
Type the message in the text box then press Enter.
Close the conversation window by clicking the “X” in the upper right
corner.
Point to a contact’s picture and click the Call button or the Video
Call button.
Click the Present button in the conversation window. Select the
Attachments tab and click Add Attachment or simply drag and drop
the file into the IM text box.
Click the Present button in the conversation window and select either
Desktop, PowerPoint, or Program.</page>
  <page p="37" label="37">37
Module 4:
In this section, you will learn more about:
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
  <page p="38" label="38">38
The CEI Human Resources team provides technical HR support to all divisions/companies under the
Cox umbrella. The team is organized into three main groups:
Need blurb here...
Cox Auto</page>
  <page p="39" label="39">39
Global HR Technology
The Cox Automotive Global HR Technology team provides division specific HR support. This group is responsible
for understanding how our systems work, not just in general, but specifically for Cox Automotive.

This group also supports the integration between our HR Technology systems and other Cox Automotive
groups, such as Legal, Finance and Technology.
CEI Owned Systems
PeopleSoft &amp; Manager Self Service
Kronos
Org Charts
Compass Taleo (Recruit &amp; Transitions)
Compass Fusion (Goals &amp; Performance, Talent
Management &amp; Succession Planning)
Compass SumTotal
Navex / Policy Tech
Spark
ATG iExpense
JJ Keller
HR Acuity
Ultipro
SAP
JobVite
Taleo Learn
Service Now – HR Portal
CAI Owned Systems
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
  <page p="40" label="40">40
Requests escalated to CEI HRTS
System
Type of Change
Kronos
Kronos
Kronos
Kronos
Kronos
Kronos
Kronos
Kronos
Kronos
Kronos
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
PeopleSoft
Taleo – ONB
Taleo – ONB
Taleo – REC
Taleo – REC
New / Modify / Delete
New / Modify / Delete
New / Modify / Delete
New / Modify / Delete
New / Replace
New
New / Update / Deactivate
New / Update / Deactivate
New
New / Modify / Delete
Reset
New / Modify / Delete
New / Modify / Delete
New / Modify / Delete
New / Update / Deactivate
New / Update / Deactivate
New / Update / Deactivate
New / Update / Deactivate
New / Update / Deactivate
New / Update / Deactivate
New / Update / Deactivate
New / Update / Deactivate
New / Update / Deactivate
New / Update / Deactivate
Reset
New
Update
New / Modify / Delete
New / Modify / Delete
Category
Setup
Setup
Setup
Setup
Setup
Security
Security
Setup
Setup
Setup
Setup
Setup
Setup
Setup
Setup
Setup
Setup
Setup
Setup
Setup
Setup
Data Entry
Security
Security
Security
Setup
Setup
Setup
Setup
Mass file load
Setup
Setup
Setup
Setup
Clock
Timestamp setup
Location setup
Department setup
Badge order
Manager access
Password reset
Pay codes
Work rules
Work group
Company
Business unit
Location
Department
Job code
Pay group
Earning / deduction codes
Action / Reason
Tax location code
Union code
Acquisition code
Corrections to data
Password resets
New user
Update user
Garnishment
LBC Directory – General
LBC Directory – Primary
LBC Directory – MDA Gatekeeper
Email upload
Mass file load Data prep upload
Mass file load
Leave plan upload
New workflow
New content
Work location
Correspondence updates
*ESC escalates to CEI HRTS via a ticket in ServiceNow
Field Type
Escalated By
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
ESC*
ESC*
ESC*
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
ESC*
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
Compensation
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech &amp;
ESC*
ESC*
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
ESC*
CAI HR Tech
n/a – ESC
processes
n/a – ESC
processes
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
CAI HR Tech
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
  <page p="41" label="41">41
Important Contacts
Department Name
ADP Tracking
Aetna (Med/Den)
PayFlex Cobra
Aetna Flex Spending
Aetna Life
Aetna LTD
Aetna RX
AP Shared Services
ATG Help Desk
ATG TRAX assistance
Bank of New York
Broadspire
Corporate HR
Corporate Payroll
Cox Headquarters
N/A
www.aetna.com
www.PayFlexDirect.com
www.aetna.com
N/A
N/A
www.aetnahomedelivery.com
apsuppliermaintenance@manheim.com

Support@beeline.com
N/A
N/A
Email
N/A
888‐553‐3449
888‐678‐7835
888/238‐6226
800‐523‐5065
800/726‐7777
866‐612‐3862
855‐435‐7772
877‐210‐5210
866‐233‐5463
800‐634‐7936
800‐301‐2552
CorporateHR@Manheim.com 678‐645‐2717
cpay.corp.payroll@coxinc.com. 678‐645‐4687
N/A
CSC‐ Customer Support Center CSC@Coxinc.com
Customer Care
EAP Magellan
Employment Pracces
HRTS
iExpense
iExpense Direct Deposit
InSite
InSite Password reset
Manheim Help Desk
Reree Services
Global Cash Paycard
Subpoena for records
Spark Password Reset
Total Rewards
Technology Provisioning
Vanguard
Verify Job
VSP Vision
W‐2 reprint
Cox Automove Global Learning
Magellanassist.com
N/A
hrtssupport@coxinc.com
N/A
apsharedservices@manheimcom

InSite.CoxEnterprises.Com
csc@coxinc.com
N/A
benefitshelp@coxinc.com
Dorcas.Morris@coxinc.com
idm@coxautoinc.com
totalrewards@manheim.com
technologyprovisioning@manheim.com

www.vanguard.com
N/A
hp://vsp.com
hps://w2.adp.com
678‐645‐0000
678‐645‐4357
866‐626‐4346
800‐888‐2273
877‐293‐0003
855‐413‐2413
678‐645‐2500
N/A
678‐645‐4357
877‐426‐9662
678‐645‐2500
877‐741‐4747
866‐395‐9200
N/A
6‐HELP/6‐4357
N/A
N/A
800‐523‐1188
800‐800‐4857
800‐877‐7195
800‐422‐9410
Onboarding
Plan # 090535
CO. Code 7720 &amp; Fax# 910‐3928159

ADP
Phone#
CQF
Mon.‐Fri. 7am to 7pm CT
Notes
Vendor# 21244
Service Staon
Timekeeping for contractors
1099 for rerees
Workers Compensaon
Corporate payroll contact
For soware related issues
Manheim Aucon
Technical Difficules
Quesons Only
Contact‐ Dorcas Morris</page>
  <page p="42" label="42">42
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
__________________________________________________________________
Cox Automove Global Learning</page>
</doc>